Guide to the Lindseth Collection of Alice Ephemera MSS.368
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Auction and Exhibit Materials, 271611
  - Subseries C: Sotheby Catalogs, 271644
    - Sotheby and Co., October 28, 29, 1968; 271914 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Sotheby and Co., July 23, 1969; 271915 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Sotheby and Co., November 3, 4, 1969; 271916 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Sotheby and Co., November 24, 1969; 271912 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Sotheby and Co., March 16, 1970; 271917 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Sotheby and Co., March 16, 1970; 271918 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Sotheby and Co., March 23, 24, 1970; 271919 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Sotheby and Co., April 19, 20, 1971; 271920 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Sotheby and Co., March 13, 14, 1972; 271921 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Sotheby and Co., February 19, 20, 21, 1973; 271922 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Sotheby's, July 24, 25, 1978; 271923 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Sotheby's, June 27, 28, 1994; 271924 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Subseries D: Parke-Bernet Catalogs, 271643
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., March 23, 1938; 271925 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., April 2, 3, 4, 1941; 271926 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., February 1, 1944; 271927 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., March 12, 13, 1945; 271928 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., April 3, 4, 1946; 271929 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., April 28, 1947; 271930 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., December 5, 6, 1949; 271931 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., April 30, May 1, 1951; 271932 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., February 26, 27, 1952; 271933 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., March 18, 19, 1952; 271934 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., April 29, 1953; 271935 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., March 1, 2, 1955; 271936 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., March 29, 30, 1955; 271937 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., April 26, 27, 1955; 271938 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., October 18, 19, 1955; 271939 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., October 16, 1962; 271940 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., December 4, 1962; 271941 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., February 19, 1963; 271942 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., October 22, 1963; 271944 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., May 12, 1964; 271945 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Subseries E: Maggs Bros. Catalogs, 271642
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 154, April 20, 1898; 271946 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 296, 1912; 271947 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 308, 1913; 271948 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 350, 1916; 271949 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 414, 1921; 271950 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 443, 1923; 271951 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 511, 1928; 271952 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 574, 1932; 271953 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 599, 1934; 271954 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 600, 1934; 271955 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 621, 1936; 271956 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 624, 1936; 271957 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 649, 1937; 271961 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 711, 1941; 271958 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 771, 1948; 271959 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 787, 1949; 271960 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 864, 1959; 271962 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 902, August 2, 1966; 271963 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 919, 1969; 271964 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 937, 1971; 271965 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 962, January 1972; 271966 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 947, October 1972; 271967 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 947, October 1972; 271968 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 1025, March 1982; 271969 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Maggs Bros.; No. 1155, March 8, 1993; 271970 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Subseries F: Exhibit Materials, 2015; 0.1 Linear Feet in one folder
    Scope and Contents
    This subseries contains exhibit cards from the Grolier Club's 2015 exhibit Alice in a World of Wonderlands: The Translations of Lewis Carroll's Masterpiece. The cards accompanied items donated by Jon Lindseth in 2015.
    - Alice in a World of Wonderlands: The Translations of Lewis Carroll's Masterpiece exhibit cards, 2015 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Series II: Housewares/Decorations, 272013
  - Subseries A: Textiles, 272015
    - Alice in Wonderland T-Shirt, 1980; 272094 (Box 16, Item 1)
      With figures based on Disney film, in box, unopened.
    - Alice in Wonderland Handkerchief 1/4, 1925; 272095 (Box 16, Item 2)
      Each handkerchief has a colorful Alice theme, with titles and the name of the artist. The borders, all different are hand-rolled. Illustrations by Gladys Peto.
      Dimensions: 9"x9"
    - Alice in Wonderland Handkerchief 2/4, 1925; 272096 (Box 16, Item 3)
    - Alice in Wonderland Handkerchief 3/4, 1925; 272097 (Box 16, Item 4)
    - Alice in Wonderland Handkerchief 4/4, 1925; 272098 (Box 16, Item 5)
    - Alice in Wonderland Pants, 1970's; 272099 (Box 16, Item 6)
      Men's bellbottom trousers.
      Dimensions: 32" waist
    - Alice in Wonderland Scarf, [Undated]; 272100 (Box 16, Item 7)
      Light green scarf
      Dimensions: 33.25"x16"
    - Alice in Wonderland Scarf, [Undated]; 272101 (Box 16, Item 8)
      Ivory silk scarf with Alice characters
      Dimensions: 33.5"x12.5"
    - Alice in Wonderland Bib, [Undated]; 272102 (Box 16, Item 9)
      Plastic baby bib (red) with Alice characters.
    - Alice in Wonderland Bib, [Undated]; 272103 (Box 16, Item 10)
      Plastic baby bib (blue) with Alice characters
    - Cloth Cocktail Napkin Set, [Undated]; 272104 (Box 16, Item 11)
      Scope and Content
      Set of 8 cloth cocktail napkins (2 Tweedledum and 2 Jabberwocky) with Alice characters.
      Dimensions: 9.5"x10"
    - Alice in Wonderland Pink Towel and Napkin Set, [Undated]; 272105 (Box 16, Item 12)
      Pink tea towel with 2 matching napkins to match.
    - Alice in Wonderland Tea Towel, [Undated]; 272106 (Box 16, Item 13)
      Tan tea towel with brown lobster and crab characters.
      Dimensions: 29"x16"
    - Alice in Wonderland Tea Towel Set, [Undated]; 272107 (Box 16, Item 14)
      8 fringed tea towels
  - Subseries B: China, 272020
    - Tenniel China 1/12, [Undated]; 272021 (Box 12, Item 1)
      Alice and the White Rabbit
      1 Plate featuring hand colored illustrations from the original engravings for Alice in Wonderland by John Tenniel.
      Dimensions: 10" Diameter
    - 2 small china spoon holders, 277625 (Box 60)
    - Tenniel China 2/12, [Undated]; 272022 (Box 12, Item 2)
      "1 Plate featuring hand colored illustrations from the original engravings for Alice in Wonderland by John Tenniel.
    - Tenniel China 3/12, [Undated]; 272023 (Box 12, Item 3)
      ''No room! No room!'' They cried out.
      D1 Plate featuring hand colored illustrations from the original engravings for Alice in Wonderland by John Tenniel.
    - Tenniel China 4/12, [Undated]; 272024 (Box 12, Item 4)
    - Tenniel China 5/12, [Undated]; 272025 (Box 12, Item 5)
      "Oh dear! Oh dear! I shall be too late!"
    - Tenniel China 6/12, [Undated]; 272026 (Box 13, Item 1)
    - Tenniel China 7/12, [Undated]; 272027 (Box 13, Item 2)
      Alice began, in a low, timid voice, "If you please, sir."
    - Tenniel China 8/12, [Undated]; 272028 (Box 13, Item 3)
    - Tenniel China 9/12, [Undated]; 272029 (Box 13, Item 4)
      "Wax-works weren't made to be looked at for nothing.''
    - Tenniel China 10/12, [Undated]; 272030 (Box 13, Item 5)
    - Tenniel China 11/12, [Undated]; 272031 (Box 13, Item 6)
      "Twinkle, twinkle little bat! How I wonder where you're at!''
    - Tenniel China 12/12, [Undated]; 272032 (Box 13, Item 7)
    - Alice in Wonderland 30th Anniversary Collector Plate, 1980-1981; 272033 (Box 14, Item 1)
      Ceramic plate numbered 2,343 in a limited edition of 7,500.
      Dimensions: 7½" diameter
    - Alice and the White Rabbit Plate, [1920]; 272035 (Box 14, Item 2)
      Hammersley bone china decorated plate, illustrations by Gladys Peto.
      Dimensions: 8.5" diameter
    - Mad Hatter's Tea Party Plate, [1920]; 272036 (Box 14, Item 3)
    - Doormouse Has a Rude Awakening Plate, [1920]; 272037 (Box 14, Item 4)
      Dimensions: 6.5" diameter
    - Mad Tea Party Plate, [Undated]; 272038 (Box 14, Item 5)
      Ironstone with Alice characters, from Johnson Bros., Stoke-on-Trent, UK.
      Dimensions: 6" diameter
    - Mad Tea Party Bowl, [Undated]; 272039 (Box 14, Item 6)
    - Mad Hatter Tea Party Saucer, [Undated]; 272040 (Box 14, Item 7)
      Hammersley bone china saucer with Mad Hatter Tea Party decorations, illustrated by Gladys Peto.
    - Mad Hatter Tea Party Plate, [Undated]; 272041 (Box 14, Item 8)
      Gold-rimmed china plate, product of Alice's Shop. Oxford, UK.
    - Mad Tea Party Cup, [1920]; 272042 (Box 14, Item 9)
      Hammersley bone china (England) decorated with Mad Hatter Tea Party, illustrated by Gladys Peto.
    - Mad Tea Party Cup, [1920]; 272043 (Box 14, Item 10)
    - Walt Disney Cup, [Undated]; 272044 (Box 14, Item 11)
      TAlice characters under tree, decorated, marked "From Pang Ma June 14/73, brought from visit to Disneyland".
    - Mad Tea Party Cup, [Undated]; 272045 (Box 14, Item 12)
      Johnson Bros. Ironstone, England
    - Alice in Wonderland Pitcher, [1920]; 272046 (Box 14, Item 13)
      Hammersley bone china pitcher, decorated, illustrations by Gladys Peto
      Dimensions: 4.5" high
    - Alice in Wonderland Toy China Tea Set, [1980]; 272047 (Box 15, Item 1)
      Alice in Wonderland toy china tea set for children, ten pieces (wrapped in tissue) in original box lettered in print Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland toy china tea set, stock no. "0223-9001". Anaheim? ca 1980? Includes: teapot, top, saucer, creamer, three teacups, and three saucers.
    - Alice et le Lapin Blanc Plate, 1981; 272048 (Box 15, Item 2)
      1 Sandy Nightingale Alice et le lapin blanc Alice and the white rabbit. Limoges: Porcelaine Georges Boyer, 1981. Ceramic plate. "Première assiette de la série 'Alice au pays des merveilles" de Sandy Nightingale. Emise à l'occasion du cent cinquantième anniversaire de la naissance de Lewis Carroll." "Numéro Bradex: 18-B61-1.1". "[L]'assiette no BY 409 fait partie d'une édition à tirage limité.
    - Alice in Wonderland Plate, [Undated]; 272049 (Box 15, Item 3)
      Reed and Barton hand crafted 'Damascene' Alice in Wonderland Plate, limited edition
      Dimensions: 11" diameter
    - Alice in Wonderland Nursery Set, [Undated]; 272050 (Box 15, Item 4)
      By Johnson Brothers, contents include: 8'' plate, baby dish, mug, and an egg cup.
  - Subseries C: Salt and Pepper Shakers, 272133
    - Porcelain Alice character salt and pepper shakers, undated; 278732 (Box 63)
    - Porcelain Alice character salt and pepper shakers, undated; 278733 (Box 59)
    - 4 Alice character salt and pepper shakers, 278734 (Box 60)
  - Subseries D: Porcelain Figurines, 272159
    - Alice Figure on Pink Pedestal, [Undated]; 272160 (Box 59)
      Alice on pink pedestal, hands behind her back.
      Dimensions: 5" tall
    - Cheshire Cat Figure, [Undated]; 272161 (Box 64)
      Pink Cheshire Cat
      Dimensions: 2.5" long
    - Alice Figure, [Undated]; 272163 (Box 64)
      Seated Alice, legs crossed
      Dimensions: 2" tall
    - Alice Figure, [Undated]; 272164 (Box 64)
    - Alice Figure, [Undated]; 272165 (Box 66)
      Seated Alice, legs under her (dark blue)
    - Alice Figure, [Undated]; 272166 (Box 66)
      Seated Alice, legs under her (light blue)
    - Alice Figure with Book, [Undated]; 272167 (Box 66)
      China Alice, seated with a book
    - White Rabbit Figure, [Undated]; 272168 (Box 66)
      One ear is missing.
      Dimensions: 6" tall
    - Mad Hatter figure by Walt Disney, 278735 (Box 64)
    - 2 small mad hatter figures, 278736 (Box 64)
    - Porcelain Alice character figurines, 278737 (Box 63)
    - Porcelain Alice character figurines, 278738 (Box 59)
    - Alice Figure by Walt Disney, [Undated]; 272171 (Box 64)
      Dimensions: 4.5" tall
    - White Rabbit Figure, [Undated]; 272172 (Box 64)
      Walt Disney painted china White Rabbit
    - Shell plate, [Undated]; 272174 (Box 60)
      Painted with Alice characters
      Dimensions: 2.5" tall
    - Alice Figure Under Tree, [Undated]; 272177 (Box 64)
      Alice under a tree with the Cheshire Cat and White Rabbit.
      Dimensions: 8" tall
    - Shell plate, 272175 (Box 60)
    - Alice Series Royal Doulton Porcelain Figures, [1960]; 272176 (Box 61)
      12 Porcelain Beswick figurines. Figures include Alice, Gryphon, 2 Frog coachmen, Red King and Queen, Dodo, 2 White Rabbits, Mock Turtle, Mad Hatter and Alice.
    - Alice Series Royal Doulton Porcelain Figures, 1970s; 277623 (Box 62)
      Beswick stand and Chesire Cat figurine and backdrop.
  - Subseries E: Accessories, 272451
    - Bronze Mad Hatter, [Undated]; 272452 (Box 65)
    - Bronze Alice, [Undated]; 272453 (Box 65)
    - Alice and the White Rabbit Belt Buckle, 1974; 272591 (Box 45, Item 1)
    - Alice and the Caterpillar Belt Buckle, 1974; 272592 (Box 45, Item 2)
    - White Rabbit Belt Buckle, 1974; 272593 (Box 45, Item 3)
    - Walrus and the Carpenter Belt Buckle, 1974; 272594 (Box 45, Item 4)
    - Caterpillar Belt Buckle, [Undated]; 272595 (Box 45, Item 5)
    - Alice in Wonderland Gold Bookmark, 1994; 272596 (Box 45, Item 6)
    - Alice in Wonderland Key Chain, [Undated]; 272597 (Box 45, Item 7)
    - White Rabbit Bottle Opener, [Undated]; 272598 (Box 45, Item 8)
      Cast-metal White Rabbit bottle opener. Reddish-brown finish.
      Dimensions: Height 5"
    - Gold-Colored Alice in Wonderland Coin, [Undated]; 272599 (Box 45, Item 9)
    - Alice in Wonderland Barrette for Hair, [Undated]; 272600 (Box 45, Item 10)
    - Alice in Wonderland Hand-Painted Pins, [Undated]; 272601 (Box 45, Item 11)
    - Alice in Wonderland Hand-Painted Pins, [Undated]; 272602 (Box 45, Item 12)
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland Pins, [1950's]; 272603 (Box 45, Item 13)
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland Pins, [1950's]; 272604 (Box 45, Item 14)
    - Walt Disney's White Rabbit Plastic Wallet, [1950's]; 272605 (Box 45, Item 15)
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland Plastic Wallet, [1950's]; 272606 (Box 45, Item 16)
    - Alice in Wonderland Red Wallet, [Undated]; 272607 (Box 45, Item 17)
      Red plastic wallet contains two plastic coins, photo and Alice in Wonderland identification card.
  - Subseries F: Soaps, 272554
    - Alice in Wonderland Permanent Picture Soap; Set of 3, [Undated]; 272555 (Box 40, Item 1)
    - Alice in Wonderland Permanent Picture Soap; Set of 3, [Undated]; 272556 (Box 40, Item 2)
    - Alice in Wonderland Permanent Picture Soap; Set of 3, [Undated]; 272557 (Box 40, Item 3)
    - Avon Products Mad Hatter Bubble Bath, 1970; 272558 (Box 40, Item 4)
    - Alice in Wonderland Soap from Crabtree and Evelyn: Alice, 1978; 272559 (Box 40, Item 5)
    - Alice in Wonderland Soap from Crabtree and Evelyn: Alice, 1978; 272560 (Box 40, Item 6)
    - Alice in Wonderland Soap from Crabtree and Evelyn: Queen of Hearts, 1978; 272561 (Box 40, Item 7)
    - Alice in Wonderland Soap from Crabtree and Evelyn: Mad Hatter, 1978; 272562 (Box 40, Item 8)
    - Alice in Wonderland Soap from Crabtree and Evelyn: Cheshire Cat, 1980; 272563 (Box 40, Item 9)
    - Parfait Alice and White Rabbit Bath Set, [1950's]; 272564 (Box 41, Item 1)
    - Parfait Mad Hatter and March Hare Bath Set, [1950's]; 272565 (Box 41, Item 2)
  - Subseries G: Ornaments, 272726
    - 4 Christmas decorations with Hangers, [Undated]; 272727 (Box 58)
      Painted wood ornaments in original box
    - Set of 32 Alice in Wonderland Chess Pieces, [Undated]; 272728 (Box 57)
    - 12 Alice and White Rabbit Ornaments, [Undated]; 272729 (Box 58)
      Printed on Card
    - Alice Ornament, [Undated]; 272730 (Box 58)
      Hand-painted Alice in Wonderland wooden figure with movable head, arms and legs
      Dimensions: 2.75" tall
    - Trainsman Ornament, [Undated]; 272731 (Box 58)
      Hand-painted Trainsman wooden figure with movable head, arms and legs
      Dimensions: 3.75" tall
    - Queen of Hearts Ornament, [Undated]; 272732 (Box 58)
      Hand-painted Queen of Hearts wooden figure with movable head, arms and legs
    - Mad Hatter Ornament, [Undated]; 272733 (Box 58)
      Hand-painted Mad Hatter wooden figure with movable head, arms and legs
      Dimensions: 6.25" tall
    - Duchess Ornament, [Undated]; 272734 (Box 66)
      Hand-painted flat wooden figure
      Dimensions: 5.5" tall
    - Tweedle Ornament, [Undated]; 272735 (Box 66)
      Wooden figure holding hands over ears
    - Walrus Ornament, [Undated]; 272736 (Box 66)
      Wood-carved figure
    - Carpenter Ornament, [Undated]; 272747 (Box 66)
      Dimensions: 6.5" tall
    - Mad Hatter Ornament, [Undated]; 272748 (Box 60)
      Plastic tree ornament
    - White Rabbit wood painted ornament, [Undated]; 272749 (Box 66)
      Dimensions: 2.5"
    - White Rabbit Tree Ornament, [Undated]; 272750 (Box 58)
      Painted wood
    - White Rabbit Ornament, [Undated]; 272751 (Box 58)
      Pewter on wood base
      Dimensions: 3.5" tall
    - Mad Hatter Ornament, [Undated]; 272752 (Box 58)
    - Queen of Hearts Ornament, [Undated]; 272753 (Box 58)
    - Alice Ornament, [Undated]; 272754 (Box 58)
      Dimensions: 3" tall
    - Mad Hatter Ornament, wooden, running, [Undated]; 272755 (Box 66)
    - Caterpillar with Hookah Ornament, [Undated]; 272756 (Box 57)
    - Painted Metal Mad Hatter Ornament, [Undated]; 272759 (Box 57)
      Dimensions: 1.75" tall
    - China Humpty Dumpty Ornament, [Undated]; 272761 (Box 57)
- Series III: Games/Dolls/Toys/Puppets, 272011
  - Subseries A: Dolls/Puppets, 272291
    - Lavander Sachet Alice, [Undated]; 272116 (Box 17, Item 1)
    - Storybook Alice Doll, [Undated]; 272117 (Box 17, Item 2)
      Dimensions: 5.25" tall
    - Wooden Alice Doll on a Pedestal, [Undated]; 272118 (Box 17, Item 3)
    - Pipe Cleaner Alice Doll, [Undated]; 272119 (Box 17, Item 4)
    - Wooden Alice Doll with Cloth Clothes, [Undated]; 272120 (Box 17, Item 5)
      Dimensions: 7" tall
    - Alice Doll with Baby Pig, [Undated]; 272121 (Box 17, Item 6)
    - Tweedle Doll, [Undated]; 272122 (Box 17, Item 7)
    - Queen of Hearts Doll, [Undated]; 272123 (Box 17, Item 8)
      Dimensions: 8.5" tall
    - Cloth Alice Doll with Yarn Hair, [Undated]; 272124 (Box 17, Item 9)
      Dimensions: 9" tall
    - White Rabbit Doll, [Undated]; 272125 (Box 18, Item 1)
      A White Rabbit stuffed animal in burlap and a Mad Hatter hat.
      Size: 14" tall
    - Alice Doll, [Undated]; 272126 (Box 18, Item 2)
      Dimensions: 18" tall
    - Alice Stuffed Doll Pattern, [Undated]; 272127 (Box 18, Item 3)
    - Alice in Wonderland Reversible Glove Puppets; Set of Two, [Undated]; 272128 (Box 18, Item 4)
    - Alice in Wonderland Finger Puppets; Set of Four, [Undated]; 272129 (Box 18, Item 5)
    - Walt Disney Alice in Wonderland Marionette, [1950's]; 272130 (Box 19, Item 1)
      Includes strings for operating, doll is in original box with instructions.
      Dimensions: 13" tall
    - Effinbee Alice in Wonderland Doll, [Undated]; 272131 (Box 19, Item 2)
      Doll in original box.
      Dimensions: 11" tall
    - Fairyland Series Alice in Wonderland Doll, [Undated]; 272132 (Box 19, Item 3)
      Doll is in original box.
  - Subseries B: Games/Puzzles, 272292
    - Alice in Wonderland Jigsaw Puzzle, [Undated]; 272293 (Box 28, Item 1)
      Container is 3" diameter x 16" high cylinder
      Dimensions: 16"x24"
    - Parker Brothers Alice in Wonderland Picture Puzzle, [Undated]; 272294 (Box 28, Item 2)
    - Alice in Wonderland Stand-Up Picture Rub-Ons, 1968; 272295 (Box 28, Item 3)
    - Alice in Wonderland Tea Time Plastic Children's Dish Set, [1940's]; 272296 (Box 28, Item 4)
    - Tweedledum Board Game; New Adventures with Alice in Wonderland, [Undated]; 272300 (Box 28, Item 5)
    - Alice in Wonderland Spin Game, [Undated]; 272317 (Box 28, Item 6)
    - Alice in Wonderland Spin Game, [Undated]; 272318 (Box 28, Item 7)
    - Alice in Wonderland Spin Game, [Undated]; 272319 (Box 28, Item 8)
    - King Sized Queen of Hearts Card Game with Illustrations from Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland, [Undated]; 272402 (Box 33, Item 1)
    - Walt Disney Alice in Wonderland Sewing Cards, 1951; 272403 (Box 33, Item 2)
    - Walt Disney Alice in Wonderland Sewing Cards, 1951; 272404 (Box 33, Item 3)
    - Alice Playing Cards, 1925; 272405 (Box 33, Item 4)
      Alice Playing Cards. This item features a complete set of 48 miniature playing cards issued by Carreras in London ca 1925. Each card has a different color illustration after Tenniel with caption.
    - Alice in Wonderland Playing Cards, [Undated]; 272408 (Box 33, Item 5)
      A set of playing cards which were used as prizes in packages of cigarettes and are similar to the set sold as games somewhat earlier.
    - Alice in Wonderland Deck and Book Set, 1996; 272414 (Box 33, Item 6)
    - Alice in Wonderland Board Game, [Undated]; 272415 (Box 33, Item 7)
    - Alice in Wonderland 96 Piece Jigsaw Puzzle, 1970; 272416 (Box 33, Item 8)
    - Lewis Carroll's Alice; A Jigsaw Puzzle with over 500 Pieces, 1977; 272417 (Box 33, Item 9)
    - Alice in Wonderland Stitch-A-Story Embroidery Set, 1969; 272418 (Box 33, Item 10)
    - Alice in Wonderland Stitch-A-Story Embroidery Set, 1969; 272419 (Box 33, Item 11)
    - 4 Preschool Mother Goose Inlaid Puzzles, [Undated]; 272422 (Box 33, Item 12)
    - Alice in Puzzleland Metal Ball Box Game [green box], [Undated]; 272429 (Box 33, Item 13)
    - Alice in Puzzleland Metal Ball Box Game [yellow box], [Undated]; 272431 (Box 33, Item 14)
    - 48 Piece Antique Replica Alice in Wonderland Notched Card Construction and Building Set; Original Illustrations in Full Color, [Undated]; 272438 (Box 33, Item 15)
    - 48 Piece Antique Replica Alice in Wonderland Notched Card Construction and Building Set; Original Illustrations in Full Color, [Undated]; 272439 (Box 33, Item 16)
    - The Pictorial Game of Alice in Wonderland from the Original Designs, [Undated]; 272440 (Box 33, Item 17)
    - The New and Diverting Game of Alice in Wonderland. 48 Pictorial Cards, [Undated]; 272441 (Box 33, Item 18)
    - Alice in Wonderland Card Game; from the Disney Film, Japanese packaging, [1950's]; 272442 (Box 33, Item 19)
    - 100 Piece Alice in Wonderland Jig-Saw Puzzle; Alice and the Thimble, [Undated]; 272443 (Box 33, Item 20)
    - 100 Piece Alice in Wonderland Jig-Saw Puzzle; Alice in Wonderland, [Undated]; 272444 (Box 33, Item 21)
    - 100 Piece Alice in Wonderland Jig-Saw Puzzle; The Herald, [Undated]; 272445 (Box 33, Item 22)
    - 100 Piece Alice in Wonderland Jig-Saw Puzzle; Alice and the Cheshire Cat, [Undated]; 272446 (Box 33, Item 23)
    - 100 Piece Alice in Wonderland Jig-Saw Puzzle; the Queen, [Undated]; 272447 (Box 33, Item 24)
    - 100 Piece Alice in Wonderland Jig-Saw Puzzle; the Queen, [Undated]; 272448 (Box 33, Item 25)
    - 100 Piece Alice in Wonderland Jig-Saw Puzzle; Alice and the Baby Pig, [Undated]; 272449 (Box 33, Item 26)
    - "Animated Alice in Wonderland Dolls" paper dolls in box, [Undated]; 272468 (Box 36, Item 1)
    - Alice in Wonderland Printing Sets in box, [Undated]; 272483 (Box 36, Item 10)
    - Walt Disney's Alice in Wonderland Balloons by Eagle, [1950's]; 272484 (Box 36, Item 11)